(Sheldon:)I'm truly worried.
I-I told you, there's
nothing to worry about.
(Sheldon:)Well, I've been
doing some research
(Sheldon:)and I've learned that
one in 700,000 people
die from general anesthesia.
Buddy, w... Do you realize that
that also means
(Leonard:)699,999 people don't die?
(Sheldon:)I suppose that's true.
(Sheldon:)You're such a glass
half-full kind of guy.
(Sheldon:)I'm going to miss that.
(Raj:)Oh, so, my, uh, parents'
40th anniversary's coming up
(Raj:)and I can't think
of a thing to get them.
(Howard:)Damn, can you imagine
(Howard:)being married to someone
for 40 years?
(Bernadette:)Not anymore.
(Raj:)Anyway, any ideas on a gift?
(Bernadette:)Well, what are some
of the things they like?
(Raj:)They used to like
going to the Mumbai Symphony,
(Raj:)but last year my mom thought
they were phoning it in.